Guide to the Leonard Solomon Silk papers, 1929-1995 and undated, bulk 1950-1985 RL.01187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 6096, 1933-1985, and undated, 86 boxes
  - Subject Files, St. Louis Model-Swiss Banks (Box 10B)
    - Structure - paper entitled: Full Employment and the New Economy, by Charles C. Killingsworth (Box 10B)
    - Surface transportation (Box 10B)
    - Sweden (Box 10B)
    - Swiss Banks (Box 10B)
  - Subject Files, Task Force-United Kingdom (Box 11A)
    - Task Force on Employment (Box 11A)
    - Taxation with representation (Box 11A)
    - Tax policies (Box 11A)
    - Taxes, two folders (Box 11A)
    - Textiles (Box 11A)
    - Trade, two folders (Box 11A)
    - Trade - Japan and other countries (Box 11A)
    - Trade policy, two folders (Box 11A)
    - Trade/preferential trading blocs (Box 11A)
    - Transfer payments (Box 11A)
    - Transportation (Box 11A)
    - Travel, receipts, etc. (Box 11A)
    - Tsai speeches 1975 - Tsai and Company, Inc. (Box 11A)
    - UNCTAD (Box 11A)
    - Unemployment, two folders (Box 11A)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 11A)
    - United Community Funds and Councils of America, Inc. (UCFCA) (Box 11A)
    - United Kingdom (Box 11A)
  - Subject files, U.S. Steel-World (Box 11B)
    - U.S. Steel (Box 11B)
    - U.S. Taxes (Box 11B)
    - U.S. Wage and price controls (newspaper clippings) (Box 11B)
    - University of Chicago (Box 11B)
    - University of Massachusetts (Box 11B)
    - University of Missouri (Box 11B)
    - Value added tax (Box 11B)
    - Vanik, Charles A. - Congress (Box 11B)
    - Vesco, Robert L. (Box 11B)
    - Vietnam (Box 11B)
    - Vietnam - economics (Box 11B)
    - Wage - price controls - 1971 Dec. (Box 11B)
    - Wage - price controls - 1971 Oct. - Nov. (Box 11B)
    - Wallace, George C. (Box 11B)
    - Weintraub, Sidney - A Feasible Anti-Inflation Incomes Policy (Box 11B)
    - Welfare, two folders (Box 11B)
    - Williams census (Box 11B)
    - World Bank (Box 11B)
    - World Bank Energy Report (Box 11B)
    - World of economics (Box 11B)
  - 1964 and 1965 income tax forms (Box 11B)
  - 52 miscellaneous folders (Box 11B)
  - Galley Proofs (Box 12)
    - An All-Volunteer Army?, Riddle, 358-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Art and the Part, Too, 474-Editorial (Box 12)
    - An Asian Anachronism, Little, Compton, Brown (Box 12)
    - Avoiding Another Money Crisis, Silk, 160-Editorial (Box 12)
    - The Busy Night, Borland, 421-Editorial (Box 12)
    - A Comeback for Cities?, A. Gleicher (Box 12)
    - Contemporary Economics Principles and Issues, Leonard Silk, McGraw-Hill Book Company, pp.ii-xiii. (Box 12)
    - Countryman, Ray Gorham (Box 12)
    - Crime, Courts and Justice, Marcinko, 458-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Deterring Skyjackers, Wellman, 405-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Editorial Page Poetry, Gleicher, 483 and 418-Editorials (Box 12)
    - Editorial Page Poetry, Lessow, 379-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Educational Isolationism, McLaughlin, 198-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Endemic Inflation, Marcinko, 9-Editorial (Box 12)
    - The Flood Plains, Schwarz (Box 12)
    - The Harmless Dragons, Riddle (Box 12)
    - Index of Key Concepts, Leonard Silk, pp.397-407, McGraw-Hill, Contemporary Economics: Principles and Issues (Box 12)
    - Inflationary Benefits, Sundholm, 1 item, 2 copies (Box 12)
    - The Kleindienst Appointment, Schwarz, Edit-Silk, 1-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Literal Equality, Riddle, 461-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Man-Made Fuel Crisis, Ray Gorham, 477-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Marketing and Advertising in the Context of the Firm-Hand, Chapter Three, Longman, 7 pages (Box 12)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York: The Morgan Guaranty Survey and World Financial Markets (Box 12)
      The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Advance Proof - For Release Nov. 21, 1975, pp. 1-11 and July 28, 1974, also World Financial Markets, Advance Proof - For Release Aug. 21, 1973, Aug. 23, 1974, pp. 1-9, and Nov. 21, 1975
    - Murders and Muggings, Freund, 274-Editorial (Box 12)
    - The New Inflation, Encounter, E.J. Mishan, March 22, 1974, pp.176-186 (Box 12)
    - Postscript to Stockholm, Rock (Box 12)
    - Price War in the Air, Ray Gorham, 75-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Readings in Contemporary Economics, Leonard Silk, pp. i-x (Box 12)
    - Save the Mason Act, Pollaro, 251-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Subject Index to book by L.S., pp. 574-590 (Box 12)
    - Tashkent to Simla, Schwarz (Box 12)
    - Time of Bounty, Pollaro, 120-Editorial (Box 12)
    - Trade with Moscow, Schwarz, 362-Editorial, 4 items (Box 12)
    - The United States of Europe and America, Leonard Silk, 4 pages (Box 12)
    - The Yemeni Fissure, Dundon, Yemen, Borwn (Box 12)
    - Warning from the IMF, Ray Gorham (Box 12)
    - White Versus Right, McLaughlin (Box 12)
    - A World Depression?, Leonard Silk (Box 12)
  - Magazines
    - The New York Review of Books (Box 12)
      Vol. XX, No. 8, May 17, 1973 and Vol. XXI, No. 12, July 18, 1974
    - The New York Times Book Review (Box 12)
      Vol. LXXV, No. 32, Aug. 9. 1970, Vol. LXXVI, No. 49 and 52, Dec. 5 and 26, 1971, and Vol. LXXVII, No. 35, Aug. 27, 1972
    - The New York Times Magazine (Box 12)
      Dec. 10 and July 2, 1972, Feb. 11 and March 11, 1973, Sept. 22, 1974, and March 2, 1975.
    - Potomac, The Washington Post, May 27, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Manuals
    - The Quality of Life Action Manual, Institute for the Quality of Life, Inc., New York, undated (Box 12)
  - Manuscripts (Box 13)
    - Berge, R. and Draayer, G. F., eds., Teaching Personal Economics in the Home Economics Curriculum, 100 pages and preface (Box 13)
    - Canfield, J., Teaching Personal Economics, 171 pages and appendix (Box 13)
    - Fersh, G. and Warmke, R. R., eds., Teaching Personal Economics in the Social Studies Curriculum, 74 pages (Box 13)
    - Friend, I. and Blume, M., Mutual Funds and Other Institutional Investors: A New Perspective, A Twentieth Century Fund Study, 299 pages, annotated (Box 13)
    - Glaser, E. C., Why and For What Purpose Does One Forecast, 16 pages (Box 13)
    - Kerman, C. E., Creative Tension: The Life and Thought of Kenneth Boulding, University of Michigan Press, Ann Arbor, 403 pages, annotated (Box 13)
  - Manuscripts (Box 14)
    - Lovenstein, M., Economics and the Consumer (Box 14)
    - Incomplete short story, no author or title mentioned, typed, undated 13 pages (Box 14)
    - One-act play, photocopy, no author or title, undated, 6 pages (Box 14)
    - Unidentified transcript, 361 pages (Box 14)
    - Silk, L.S., Partial book manuscript 700 pages, annotated (Box 14)
  - Manuscripts (Box 15)
    - The Rhythm of Nixonomics, undated, photocopy annotated, 16 pages (Box 15)
    - Silk, L. S., Nixonomics, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Silk, L. S., Veblen - A Play in Three Acts, typed, undated, annotated, 145 pages (Box 15)
    - Warmke, Roman R., Ed., Teaching Personal Economics in the Business Education Curriculum, 141 pages (Box 15)
  - Memoranda, 1944 March 8-1975 November 21 and undated (Box 15)
    Early memoranda are between military personnel, including Leonard S. Silk, as well as faculty and students at the Juilliard School of Music. Later memoranda are primarily between members of corporations and periodicals, some of which include Leonard S. Silk. Individuals include Charles L. Schultze, Bankers Trust Co., Jerome M. Rosow, C. F. McNeil, New York Times, Times staff, Members of the U.S. Senate, Arnold A. Saltzman, Delafield Childs, Inc., Goldman, Sachs and Co., Committee for Economic Development, and Morgan Stanley and Co.
    - Levy, W. J., Consultants Corporation, New York, Future OPEC Accumulation of Oil Money: A New Look at a Critical Problem, June 1975 (Box 15)
    - Lubow, Oscar, A Prospectus for a Multi-Disciplined Business Professional Service Organization, draft memo (Box 15)
    - Owen, Bruce, et al, Studies in the Economics of Mass Communication, memorandum No. 99 - A Selected Bibliography in the Economics of the Mass Media, Aug. 1970 (Box 15)
  - Newsletters (Box 15)
    - Aesthetic Realism Foundation, Inc., The Right of Aesthetic Realism to Be Known, No. 1, April 4, 1973; No. 73, Vol. II, No. 21, Aug 21, 1974; and No. 95, Vol. II, No. 43, Jan. 22, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Association for the Study of the Grants Economy, ASGE Newsletter, No. 3, Dec. 1, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Book Times, No. 16, June 1970 (Box 15)
    - British Information Services, Policy and Reference Division, July 8 and Sept. 4, 1970, Aug. 19 1073, and Nov. 13 (two copies), Nov. 20 and Nov. 14, 1975 (Box 15)
    - British Record, No. 7, June 25, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce, Commercial Letter, Toronto, Sept.-Oct. 1972 (Box 15)
    - Congressional Quarterly Inc., News Futures, June 21, 1972 (Box 15)
    - Data Resources, Inc., Aug. 15, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Economic Research Department, Weekly Economic Package, Nov. 11, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Newsletters (Box 16)
    - Economic Week - EW, Sept. 3, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Lionel D. Edie and Company, Inc., July 30, 1973 (Box 16)
    - The Emergency Committee for American Trade, Reasons Why The 1969 Trade Bill is Important to the U.S. Economy and the U.S. Consumer, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 16)
    - Council for European Studies, European Studies Newsletter, Vol. II, No. 3, Dec. 1972 (Box 16)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis, U.S. Financial Data, released May 22, 1970; Week Ending: June 24, 1970 and Feb. 3, 1971 (Box 16)
    - First National City Bank, New York, Energy memo, Vol. VI, No. 3, July 1970, cover letter attached, and Monthly Economic Letter, March 1974, and Nov. 1975 (Box 16)
    - German Press Review, Sept. 11, 1974 (Box 16)
    - The Janeway Letter, no. 1033, March 25, 1969, and No. 1048, July 8, 1969 (Box 16)
    - McGraw-Hill News, Vol. 2, No. 20, May 18, 1961 and Vol. 7, No. 20, May 19, 1966 (2 copies) (Box 16)
    - Salomon Brothers, Newsletter, No. 5, June 1974 (Box 16)
    - Self-Management Newsletter, No. 1, June 1973 (Box 16)
    - Today's British Papers, July 8, 1970, July 2, 1974, July 29, 1974, Aug. 21, 1974, and Sept. 11-12, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Turning Points, Monthly Newsletter, July 1, 1970 (Box 16)
    - United States Department of Commerce News, Washington, D.C., for release Aug. 14, 1970 (Box 16)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Office of Information, news, newsletters:
      - Women's Bureau - July 14, 1970 and July 16, 1970, 5 items (Box 16)
      - Bureau of Labor Statistics - Aug. 5, 1970, June 21, 1972 (2 copies) and July 1973 (Box 16)
      - Manpower Administration - Aug. 5, 1970 (Box 16)
      - Other - June 22, 23 (2 copies), 24 and 26, 1972 and Sept. 3, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 16)
    - In envelope, 43 items (Box 16)
    - Related to economics, 161 items (Box 16)
    - Related to other subjects, 81 items (Box 16)
    - Magazine clippings, 82 items (Box 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 17 A and B)
    - Editorial Page - New York Times, 1,313 items (Box 17 A and B)
  - Newspapers (Box 18)
    - The Daily Cardinal, University of Wisconsin, Vol. XLVIII, No. 180, June 2, 1939 (Box 18)
    - The Guild Reporter, Official Organ of the Newspaper Guild, AFL-CIO, CLC, Vol. XL, No. 11, June 8, 1973 (Box 18)
    - Hamevaser, Yeshiva University, New York, Vol. VIII, NO. 4, Dec. 1969, Vol. VIII, No. 6, April 1970, and Vol. IX, No. 1, May 1970 (Box 18)
    - Headlines, General Electric, Vol. II, No. 35, Sept. 22, 1975 (Box 18)
    - Hillel Review, Madison, Vol. XIV, No. 11, March 10, 1939 (Box 18)
    - The Japan Economic Journal, Vol. 9, No. 460-463, 466-467, Oct. 19 and 26, Nov. 2 (2 copies), Nov. 9 and 30 (2 copies), and Dec. 7, 1971, and Vol. 10, No. 179, Feb. 29, 1972 (Box 18)
    - The Japan Economic Review, Vol. 4, No. 5, May 15, 1972 (Box 18)
    - Look Japan, The Newspaper of Industry, Vol. 17, No. 193, May 10, 1972 (Box 18)
    - More - A Journalism Review, Vol. 2, No. 7, July 1972 (Box 18)
    - The New York Times Student Weekly, Section II, Oct. 26, 1970 (Box 18)
    - The Simmons News, Vol. XXVII, No. 17, 1949 and No. 19, March 23, 1950 (Box 18)
    - The Staff Daily, Madison, Wisconsin, No. 22, May 25, 1938 (Box 18)
    - The Times, Japan - A Special Report, May 8, 1972 (Box 18)
    - Times Talk, Vol. 23, No. 7, Jan. 1972 (Box 18)
  - Notebooks (Box 18)
    - Notebooks and notepads, 11 items (Box 18)
    - The Wage and Price Control Institute, black notebook (Box 18)
  - Volunteer Oil Industry Communications Effort, Let's Talk Oil, Washington, D.C., Sept. 1971 (Box 19)
  - Notes
    - Wilson, I. H., Briefing Notes on Business Environment Study of the Future Course and Impact of Inflation, photocopy, 4 pages, May 18, 1970 (Box 19)
    - Notes from Corporate Reports of S.E.A.C. Members Relating to "The Information Process", undated (Box 19)
    - G. Tsai and Company, Inc., New York, July 22, 1974 (3 copies) and July 2, 1975 (2 copies) - notes taken at the Regency Hotel, New York City, at weekly meeting held, from Leonard Silk's Talk (Box 19)
  - Occasional Papers, Committee for Economic Development (CED)
    - Appendices A-E from CED Policy Statement, A: Further Weapons Against Inflation, 1970; B-E: High Employment Without Inflation, 1972, xerox (Box 19)
    - CED press release, June 29, 1972, June 17, 1974, and July 16, undated (Box 19)
    - CED in 1969 - Resolving Conflicts over National Goals, New York, report of activities (Box 19)
    - Congressional Decision Making for National Security, Sept. 1974 (Box 19)
    - Economic Growth in the United States, Oct. 1969 (Box 19)
    - Economic Literacy of Americans - A Program for Schools and for Citizens, 1962 (Box 19)
    - Educating Tomorrow's Managers...The Business Schools and the Business Community, Oct. 1964 (Box 19)
    - Further Weapons Against Inflation - Measures to Supplement General Fiscal and Monetary Policies, Nov. 1970 (Box 19)
    - High Employment Without Inflation - A Positive Program for Economic Stabilization, A statement by the Research and Policy Committee, July 1972 (Box 19)
    - Improving the Public Welfare System, A statement by the Research and Policy Committee, April 1970, 2 copies (Box 19)
    - International Economic Consequences of High-Priced Energy, Sept. 1975 (Box 19)
    - The Management and Financing of Colleges, Oct. 1973 (Box 19)
  - Panel Discussions, 28 items
    - Information process - impacts on policy-making centers during the next twenty years, undated (Box 26)
    - U.S. foreign policy lectures, Cornell, 1975 (Box 151)
      Folder contains some correspondence related to a series of lectures at Cornell, 1975, on U.S. foreign policy (later a book edited by Rosecrance), a list of presenters, and substantial lecture drafts by Silk, Richard Rosecrance, Coral Bell, Alastair Buchan, Pierre Hassner.
  - Papers
    - Aaron, H., New Views of Property Tax Incidence, 24 pages (Box 26)
    - " Why is Welfare So Hard to Reform? Staff paper, Studies in Social Economics, Brookings Institution, 1973 (Box 26)
    - " and von Furstenberg, G., How Inefficient are the Transfers in Kind: The Case of Housing Assistance, undated, 16 pages (Box 26)
    - Allied Chemical Corporation Planning Economics Department, Consumer Expenditures Through the 1970s, April 15, 1970. 27 pages (Box 26)
    - Ando, A. K., and Modigliani, F., Consumption and Consumer Expenditure, Appendix A. 23 pages, mimeo, annotated, undated (Box 26)
    - Armstrong, R. B., Linking Skills, Jobs and Housing in the New York Urban Region, March 1972, 36 pages (Box 26)
    - Bach, G. L. The Search for Stability - What Have We Learned? undated, 15 pages (Box 26)
    - Barber, J. D., Thoughts on Man and the Information Process, 6 pages mimeo, undated (Box 26)
    - Behr, R. M. and Kupperman, R. H., International Computer Conferencing: A Promising Tool of Diplomacy, 10 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Bernstien, P. L., Is the President on the Right Track? August 13, 1974. 3 pages typescript (Box 26)
    - Bloomfield, A. I., European Monetary Integration: The Historical Setting, undated, 41 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Bosworth, B., Background Paper for April 3rd Meeting, Committee for Economic Development, March 1975. 6 pages (Box 26)
    - " Topical Agenda of Past and Future Subcommitte Meetings, Committee for Economic Development, March 1975, 9 pages (Box 26)
    - Bower, R. and Menge J., Regulation, Competition, and the Computer Services Industry. Project proposal - Economic Studies Program, December 1969, 5 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Branson, W.H. Summary Fiscal Flexibility and the Economic Experience of the 1960s and Early 1970s. June 1974, 7 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Broehl, W. G., Jr., The Business and Society Course in the Business Schools, April 1965, in binder, mimeo (Box 26)
    - The Brookings Institution, Studies in the Regulation of Economic Activity, August 1969, 31 pages photocopy (Box 26)
    - Businessmen's Advisory Committee, Committee on Economic Policy Studies, Policy Recommendation, undated, 7 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Center for Policy Research, Inc., Preliminary Findings of Electronic Town Hall Project (Minerva). For release on January 14, 1973. 16 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Coleman, J. R., Economic Understanding and Social Values: Can There be a Consensus Any Longer? undated, 12 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Committee for Economic Development, Further Weapons Against Inflation: Measures to Supplement General Fiscal and Monetary Policies. September 14, 1970, 86 pages, 2 copies (Box 26)
    - Improving Productivity in State and Local Government. A draft proposal to be considered at meeting on November 19, 1975. 86 pages, 2 copies (Box 26)
    - Social Responsibilities of Business Corporation. Confidential voting copy of the Statement on National Policy approved by the Research and Policy Committee of CED on May 5, 1971. 62 pages xerox (Box 26)
    - A Consortium of Wilsey and Ham; Kelso, Cotton, Seligman and Ray; 2nd Optimum Systems, Inc., Operation Breakthrough Type B Proposal, Part I. Technical and Management Submission RFP H-55-69... 43 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Cooper, Richard N., European Monetary Unification and Integration of the World Economy, August 1972, 25 pages mimeo, annotated (Box 26)
    - Corden, W.M., Oxford University, Monetary Integration and the Adjustment Problem, undated, 19 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Crowther, G., 1938-1956 A Retrospect, undated, 5 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Darby, Mochael R., The Equilibrium Price Level and the Effects of Price and Wage Controls: The First Two Years, October 3, 1971. 51 pages xerox (Box 26)
    - Davis, O. A and K.O. Kortanel, Centralization and Decentralization the Political Economy of Public School Systems, undated, 20 pages (Box 26)
    - Denison, Edward F. How to Raise the High Unemployment Growth Rate By one Percentage Point, undated, 17 pages annotated (Box 26)
    - Eads, G., The Local Service Airline Experiment After Twenty Five Years: An Assessment, September 1970, 11 pages xerox (Box 26)
    - Eastburn, D. P., Draft for article, August 10, 1973, 3 pages mimeo and attached letter regarding article (Box 26)
    - Eisner, R., The War and the Economy. Prepared for Why Are We Still In Vietnam, to be published by Random House, 21 pages mimeo (Box 26)
    - Feige, Edgar L. and D. K. Pierce, The U.S. Wage Price controls Experiment; Did it Work? April 1973, 32 pages (Box 26)
    - Feldstein, M., On the Effects of the Income Tax Treatment of Charitable Contributions: Some Preliminary Results, undated, 49 pages xerox (Box 26)
    - Frankel, M. L., Economics Education: 1969 and Beyond, undated, 15 pages (Box 26)
    - Friend, I., Methodology in Finance, December 28, 1792. 26 pages photocopy (Box 26)
  - Papers (Box 27)
    - Gale, B. T., Market Share and Rate of Return, undated, 32 pages (Box 27)
    - Gennard, J., Multinational Corporations and British Labour: A Review of Attitudes and Responses. January 1972. printed (Box 27)
    - Georgescu-Roegen, N., Analysis Versus Dialectics in Economics. Separata do livro Ensaios Economicos, Homenagen a Octavio Gouvea de Bulhones, editado pela APEC Editora S.A., Rio de Janeiro, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Gilpin, R., Multinational Corporations and American Foreign Policy, undated, 24 pages, mimeo, annotated (Box 27)
    - Glaser, E. L., The Information Technology Panel - Prediction on Information Technology and Its Potential Interaction with Society, undated, 24 pages mimeo (Box 27)
    - Goldfinger, N., An American Trade Union View of International Trade and Investment, AFL-CIO Research Department, October 1971, 21 pages mimeo (Box 27)
    - Gordon, M. J., Towards a Theory of Financial Distress, undated, 17 pages mimeo (Box 27)
    - Gregory, B. M., Cable Television and the Copyright Problem. May 1, 1969, 27 pages (Box 27)
    - Gunning, J.W. et al., The Price of Energy and Potential Growth of Developed Countries, An Attempt at Quantification. 45 pages xerox, annotated (Box 27)
    - Heilbroner, R. L., Has Capitalism a Future? undated, 23 pages mimeo (Box 27)
    - Hudson, M. W., Briefing Paper-Persistent Global Inflation: Causes and Consequences, May 27, 1974. 19 pages xerox (Box 27)
    - Institute for the Quality of Life, Inc., Quality of Life, Community Surveys, the IQoL Community Survey - what it is and how it is conducted, prepared for Leonard Silk, undated, 6 pages (Box 27)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development. Publicized Euro-Currency Credits to Developing Countries During 1973, preliminary, March 12, 1974, 14 pages (Box 27)
    - Publicized Euro-Currency Credits During 1973 to Countries not Members of the World Bank, preliminary, March 20, 1974, 5 pages (Box 27)
    - Japan Society, Inc., Committee on Economic Policy Studies, Summary Findings, undated 6 pages xerox (Box 27)
    - Joshi et al, Urbanization and Employment in Abijan. Working papers, Geneva, October 1974 (Box 27)
    - Kaplan, A.D.H., Big Enterprise in a Competitive System. Revised edition, Brookings Institution, May 1964 (Box 27)
    - Kaufmann, William W. Alternative Post Vietnam Defense Budgets, Draft, undated, 33 pages (Box 27)
    - The General Purpose Forces: The Non-nuclear Component, draft, undated, 67 pages, 2 copies (Box 27)
    - Kindleberger, C. P. The Clash of Economics, Sociology and Politics in the Internationalization of Business. Discussion paper, no. 4, February 1972. 41 pages mimeo (Box 27)
    - Kronish, Sidney J. Money and Banking. Mimeograph, pp I-1 to IV-23, undated (Box 27)
    - Larner, R., Public Policy in the Ocean Freight Industry: Regulation or Competition? June 30, 1971. First Draft, 42 pages mimeo (Box 27)
    - LaRue, et al., Calculation of New Oil Costs, United States, Years 1959 through 1974. May 1, 1975. 87 pages xerox (Box 27)
    - Levy, M. E., Constraining Inflation: Concerns, Complacencies, and Evidence, October 1975, 9 pages mimeo and cover letter (Box 27)
    - Levy, W. J., An Approach to Energy Policy for Oil Importing Countries, New York, October 1973. 15 pages (Box 27)
  - Papers (Box 28)
    - Lewis, R. G., A Proposal for Opportunity Homesteads, August 25, 1965. 19 pages (Box 28)
    - McGarrah, R. E., How International Business Could Transform the Arms Race, April 21, 1970. 19 pages (Box 28)
    - McGuire, T. W., Controls and Expectations: A Preliminary and Incomplete Draft, October 21, 1973, 21 pages (Box 28)
    - McKie, J. W. Regulation and the Free Market: The Problem of Boundaries. Incomplete, pp.1-41, undated mimeo (Box 28)
    - March, M. S., Federal Budget Priorities for Research and Development, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Marx, L., Here It Comes, But Don't Let It Worry You. April 25, 1970. 3 pages (Box 28)
    - Mayers, E. G., Long Term Economic Outlook, undated, 15 pages typescript (Box 28)
    - Minsky H.P., Fundamental Reappraisal of the Discount Mechanism, Financial Instability Revisited: the Economics of Disaster. Revised January 1970, 46 pages (Box 28)